Guide to the Edwin Patrick Kilroe Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: Index of Volumes I-XVIII
  - McCrystal, Elizabeth In file No. 1217
  - McCullen, E. Pages 880 | 909
  - McDermott, John Page 836
  - McDonald, A.N. Page 836
  - McDonald, Arthur Pages 780 | 781
  - McDonald, A.W. Page 768
  - McDonald, George Page 772
  - McDonald, William (McDonald & Mahier) Pages 906 | 909 | 937
  - McGirk, Jonce I. Page 742
  - McGirr, Newman F. Pages 742 | 766
  - McGown, Mr. Page 574
  - McGuirn, James Page 572
  - McIlwain, H.R. Pages 472-473
  - McKennis, Herbert Page 661
  - McLurg, A.C. & Co. Page 661
  - McManus, Terrance K. Pages 880 | 906
  - McMillan, A.G. Page 823
  - McMillan, J.A. Pages 643 | 661
  - McQuaid, William A. Pages 662 | 822 | 836
  - McRea, Nelson G. Pages 233a | 270 | 570 | 572 | 661 | 742
  - McReynolds, George Pages 271-274 | 671
  - McSham, B.M. Page 575
  - McVey, John J. Pages 908 | 922
  - MacAlarney, Robert E. Page 570
  - MacDonald, Arthur H. Pages 574 | 575 | 576 | 577 | 634 | 661 | 662 | 688 | 742 | 798
  - MacDonald, A.N. Pages 880 | 939 | 940
  - MacDonald & Maier Page 845
  - Mackey, J.J., Jr. Page 647
  - MacMillan Publishing Co. Pages 517 | 574 | 575 | 629 | 662 | 699 | 707
  - Macy, R.H. & Co. Pages 880 | 939 | 940
  - Madigan, F. Page 275
  - Magazine of American History Pages 276 | 562 | 575 | 610
  - Mahler, Fred G. Pages 822 | 823 | 836 | 837
  - Mahoney, W.H. Pages 743 | 767
  - Maknen, Christine Page 780
  - Malia, William H. Pages 877 | 878 | 906 | 909
  - Malkan, Henry Page 626
  - Mallon, George Page 742
  - Manhattan Club (Secretary of) Page 661
  - Mann, A.O. Page 743
  - Mann, Charles A. Page 739
  - Marchmont, John H. Page 837
  - Marks, Harry F. Page 662
  - Marshall Page 780
  - Martin, Francis Page 798
  - Martin, Francis In file No. 1217
  - Martin, J. Willis Pages 823 | 837
  - Martin, John Pages 576 | 661
  - Martine, James E. Page 576
  - Maryland, Executive Department of Page 655
  - Maryland Historical Society Page 577
  - Maryland, Secretary of State of Page 691
  - Mason, William Page 726
  - Massachussets, Colonial Society of Page 705
  - Massachussets Historical Society Pages 233a | 435a | 601 | 644 | 646 | 661 | 689 | 691 | 697e | 701a | 706
  - Massachussets, Secretary of State of Pages 654 | 691
  - Mather, C.W. Pages 17-18
  - Matthews, Albert Pages 572 | 575 | 661 | 688 | 690 | 697a | 697b | 780
  - Matthews, Annie Page 798
  - Matthews, Annie In file No. 1217
  - Matthews, Brander Pages 283 | 518
  - Mawer, H.E. Page 755
  - Mead, James M. In file No. 1217
  - MeHaysin, H. Page 725
  - "Menace" The Page 574
  - Mendoza Book Co. Pages 284 | 286 | 574 | 576 | 743 | 766 | 772 | 780 | 789 | 808
  - Mercer, Henry C. Pages 287 | 294
  - Mercury Publishing Co. Pages 295 | 296
  - Meritt, E.B. Page 823
  - Merritt, Edward L. Page 577
  - Merwin Sales Co. Pages 297 | 298 | 516d | 572 | 574 | 575 | 576 | 619 | 625
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Pages 299 | 304 | 567 | 576 | 577
  - Meurlin, William D. Pages 823 | 837
  - Meurline, M. Page 881
  - Meyer, Adolph G. Pages 661 | 780
  - Meyer, H.H.B. Pages 248 | 264a | 697c
  - Meyer, Robert Page 787
  - Meyers, John Caldwell Page 909
  - Middletown (NY) Times-Press Page 305
  - Miller, O.V. Pages 574 | 575
  - Minnesota University Page 553
  - Minnisink Valley Historical Society Pages 105 | 108
  - Minutes of Common Council Page 860
  - Mischler, Wendell W. Pages 661 | 676
  - Missouri Historical Society Pages 732 | 736
  - Missouri, (Secretary of State of) Pages 654 | 691
  - Mitchell Campaign Slush Fund Page 815
  - Moley, Raymond Pages 837 | 876A
  - Montgomery, Thomas L. Pages 372 | 738 | 775
  - Moravian Historical Society Page 306
  - Morgan, H. Gibbes, Jr. Pages 307-309
  - Morris Book Shop Pages 661 | 742 | 759 | 761 | 766 | 780 | 808
  - Morrison, Noah F. Pages 310-311a | 436a | 574 | 575 | 576 | 577 | 614 | 625 | 661 | 662 | 688 | 698 | 721 | 722 | 723 | 725 | 759 | 769 | 824
  - Morton, Jennie C. Page 312
  - Mullan, John A. Page 837
  - Mulligan, H. Page 654
  - Mulqueen, Michael J. Pages 313-314
  - Municipal Reference Library Page 817
  - Munro, R.F. Pages 789 | 798
  - Munsey, Frank A. & Co. Pages 314-316a
  - Munsey's Magazine Page 572
  - Murphy, Charles F. Page 572
  - Murphy, Richard C. Page 798
  - Museum of Natural History Pages 317 | 572 | 694
  - Myers, Albert C. Page 318
  - Myers, Gustavus Pages 319 | 574 | 575
  - Nash, Charles Page 694
  - Nation (The) Pages 320 | 582
  - National American Society Pages 636 | 653 | 882 | 907
  - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor Page 670
  - National Democratic Club Page 854
  - National Democratic Magazine Page 786 | 837
  - National Museum of U.S. Page 689
  - National Quarterly Review Page 321
  - Naumburg, Bernard Page 824
  - Naval Records and Library Page 826
  - Neale (Walter) Publishing Co. Pages 581 | 582 | 629 | 634
  - Neely, M.M. Page 798
  - Neely, M.M. In file No. 1217
  - Nelke, David G. Page 653
  - Nelson, Charles A. Pages 656 | 694
  - Nelson, Peter Page 738
  - Nelson, William Page 520
  - Neumann Bros. Pages 578 | 582
  - Nevins, Allen Page 837
  - Nevins, Mary R. Page 824
  - New Jersey Historical Society Pages 316a | 322-325 | 581 | 582 | 849
  - Newman, Charles Pages 326-328
  - New York American Page 580
  - New York Atheletic Club Page 329
  - New York Book Mark Co. Page 666
  - New York City Page 860
  - New York Civic League Page 582
  - New York Democrat Pages 880 | 934
  - New York Evening Sun Page 823
  - New York Historical Society Pages 329b | 581 | 582 | 597 | 608 | 623 | 653 | 667 | 676 | 706 | 740 | 758 | 762 | 770 | 773 | 783 | 811 | 826 | 846 | 933
  - New York Historical Society In file No. 1507
  - New York Hospital (Society of) Pages 654 | 688
  - New York Press Pages 580 | 581
  - New York Public Library Pages 329b | 569 | 580 | 581 | 582 | 626 | 666 | 668 | 694 701 | 736 | 740 | 759 | 769 | 770 | 776 | 784 | 786 | 796 | 821
  - New York Public Library In file No. 1507
  - New York Secretary of State Pages 336-337
  - New York Society Library Pages 581 | 610 | 736
  - New York State Adjutant-General Page 329a
  - New York State Board of Education Page 665
  - New York State Historian Page 557
  - New York State Historian In file No. 1507
  - New York State Historical Association Pages 880 | 922
  - New York State Library Pages 316a | 330-335 | 542 | 569 | 580 | 581 | 606 | 607 | 611 | 668 | 676 | 694 | 736 | 738
  - New York State Library In file No. 1507
  - New York Times Pages 813 | 815
  - New York Tribune Page 557
  - New York University Page 569
  - New York Young Democratic Club Pages 653 | 674
  - New York Zoological Gardens (Director of) Pages 694 | 697b
  - Nickel, Margaret C. Page 878
  - Niel Morrow Ladd Co. Pages 578 | 579
  - Nineteenth Century Magazine Page 338
  - Noonan, Rev. James E. In file No. 1507
  - Norris, Henry L. Page 329a
  - North American Review Page 339
  - North Carolina Historical Commission Pages 340-341
  - North Carolina (Secretary of State of) Page 647
  - North Carolina State Library Pages 342-343
  - Norwood Press Page 344
  - Nugent, M. In file No. 1507
  - Numismatic and Antiquarian Society Page 580
  - Nutt, Charles Pages 759 | 770
  - Nutt, Dorothy M. Page 770
  - O'Beirne, N. Page 773
  - O'Brien Michael J. Pages 884 | 908
  - O'Brien Michael J. In file No. 1507
  - O'Byrne, M.A. Page 670
  - O'Connor, James In file No. 1217
  - O'Connor, R.D.W. Pages 340 | 341
  - O'Day, Harry Page 586
  - O'Dell, G.C. Page 94
  - O'Dell, George C.D. Pages 824 | 837
  - Ogden, C.K. Page 908
  - O'Gormon, James A. Pages 585 | 586
  - O'Gormon, James A., Jr. Pages 824 | 837
  - Ohio Chemical & Manufacturing Co. Page 846
  - Ohio Historical Society Pages 345 | 643
  - Ohio (Secretary of State of) Pages 645 | 691
  - Ohio State Library Pages 346-350
  - Ohio State University Pages 567 | 569 | 608
  - Ohman Map Co. Pages 584 | 613 | 624
  - O'Keefe, David Pages 646 | 692 | 745
  - Old Ann Street Book Store Page 800
  - Olvany, George W. Pages 824 | 837
  - Oppenheim, S. Page 587
  - Oregon State Library Pages 351-353
  - Osborn, Carl H. Page 584
  - Osgood, Herbert L. Pages 407a | 516d | 584 | 587
  - O'Toole, John A. Page 586
  - Ousterhoudt, E. Howard Pages 641 | 689 | 691
  - Outlook Pages 354 | 584 | 586
  - Owen, Thomas M. Pages 355-356
  - Pach Bros. Pages 589 | 610 | 623 | 624 | 626 | 665 | 706 | 707 | 761
  - Padgett, L.P. Page 589
  - Page, Walter Hines Page 586
  - Paltsits, Victor Hugo Pages 357-360 | 668 | 670 | 694 | 883 | 908
  - Paltsits, Victor Hugo In file No. 1507
  - Paramount Famous Lasky Corp. Page 825
  - Park Board, City of New York Pages 820 | 821
  - Patjens, William S. Page 733
  - Patterson, Richard C. Pages 589 | 884
  - Patton, A. Page 361
  - Paxson, Henry Pages 587 | 824 | 837 | 838
  - Payne, Kirby Pages 586 | 589
  - Pearson's Magazine Pages 362 | 586
  - Pell, Herbert C. Pages 798 | 838
  - Pell, Herbert C. In file No. 1217
  - Penfield, Miss Georgia M. Pages 644 | 693
  - Pennsylvania Historical Commission Pages 884 | 908 | 910
  - Pennsylvania Historical Society Pages 363-369a | 589 | 670 | 724 | 736 | 738 | 740
  - Pennsylvania (Secretary of State of) Pages 654 | 691
  - Pennsylvania State Library Pages 370-373a | 736 | 738
  - Perilli, John W. Page 798
  - Perkinson, Edward K. Page 8
  - Peters, I.J. Pages 572 | 575
  - Philhower, Charles A. Pages 789 | 798
  - Phipps, Frank H. Page 589
  - Pidgeon, Jose E. Page 587
  - Pierce, John Pages 669 | 693 | 746 | 747 | 748 | 749 | 751 | 752 | 753 | 754 | 778
  - Pierce & Scopes Pages 669 | 693 | 701 | 746-754 | 761 | 764 | 771 | 778 | 779 | 786 |805
  - Pitske, Edgar Page 670
  - Platt, Chester C. Page 403a
  - Polhemus Printing Co. Page 806
  - Political News Page 838
  - Political Review Page 773
  - Political Science Quarterly Pages 585 | 908
  - Pollack, Jack J., Jr. Page 838
  - Pollock, Henry W. Pages 585 | 589
  - Pollock, James K. Page 876A
  - Pope, Miss. Page 838
  - Port of New York Authority Page 817
  - Porter, George H. Page 670
  - Post (NY) Page 582
  - Postley's Art Shop Pages 420 | 421 | 762 | 769 | 806
  - Powers Photo Engraving Co. Pages 624 | 810
  - Pratt, Enoch Free Library (Baltimore, MD) Pages 420-421
  - Press Illustrating Service Page 770
  - Press (NY) Pages 580 | 581
  - Prince, Alfred C. Pages 794 | 798
  - Prince, John D. Pages 96a | 520 | 816 | 837
  - Princeton University (Library of) Page 670
  - Prison Ship Martyrs Association Pages 647 | 670
  - Public Ledger Co. Page 789
  - Public Opinion Page 375
  - Putnam, Herbert Pages 249-256
  - Putnam's Sons (G.P.) Pages 96a | 376 | 517 | 588 | 589 | 598 | 631 | 635 | 665 | 666 | 670 | 707 | 884 | 908
  - Pyne, Walter Page 589
  - Quinn, E.F. Page 377
  - Quinn, T.C. Page 676
  - Rabenold, E. Pages 635 | 671
  - Radin, Herman T. Page 785
  - Ragan, Heartsil In file No. 1217
  - Rainey, Henry T. Page 799
  - Rainey, Henry T. In file No. 1217
  - Randell, E.O. Page 643
  - Random, William F. Page 755
  - Ray, P.O. Pages 655 | 672 | 695 | 755 | 784 | 798 | 799 | 838
  - Rayens, M.W. Pages 671 | 722
  - Raymond, J.G. Page 591
  - Readie, William Cooper Page 671
  - Receipts Pages 514-516
  - Redfield, William C. Page 591
  - Reeder, O.W. Page 607
  - Reich, O. Pages 378 | 590
  - Renwick, William W. Pages 116a-c | 379
  - Republican County Committee Pages 531 | 567 | 614 | 642 | 815
  - Republican Watchman Page 908
  - Review of Reviews Pages 884 | 908 | 922 | 928
  - Reynolds, Mary R. Page 590
  - Reynolds, W.M. Pages 539 | 591
  - Rhode Island Historical Society Pages 380-392 | 523 | 534 | 535 | 537 | 589 | 591 | 622 | 627 | 635 | 644 | 654 | 725 | 731 | 734 | 776 | 796
  - Rhode Island (Secretary of State of) Page 691
  - Rhode & Haskins Pages 400 | 403a | 591 | 708
  - Richards, Frederick B. Pages 880 | 922
  - Richardson, Frank P. Page 769
  - Richmond Sales Co. Page 393
  - Rider, S.S. Pages 394 | 394a
  - Ritchie, Albert C. In file No. 1217
  - Roberts, D.E. Pages 664 | 697c
  - Roberts, Miss Jane E. Pages 641 | 689
  - Robinson, E.R. Pages 96a | 395-399a-b | 590 | 591 | 623 | 671 | 672 | 689 | 701a | 707 | 708
  - Robinson, Elizabeth Page 316a
  - Robinson, Joe T./Walter Page 773
  - Rochester, University of Page 643
  - Rodgers, C.E. Pages 644 | 697
  - Roesch, George F. Pages 597 | 671 | 672
  - Rogers Cartoons Page 881
  - Romeike, Henry Pages 590 | 755
  - "Room 37" Page 607
  - Roose, J.M. Page 590
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Page 755
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Mrs.) Pages 824 | 838
  - Root, Elihu Pages 584 | 591
  - Rosann, W. Page 896
  - Rosenheim, Sidney T. Page 784
  - Rueff, A.E. Pages 824 | 838
  - Rumney, John D. Page 852
  - Rush, Thomas E. Page 838
  - Ryan, Daniel L. Pages 787 | 799
  - Sabin, Joseph F. Page 404
  - Sage (Russell) Foundation Pages 405 | 406
  - St. John, Sterling Page 592
  - St. Louis Public Library Page 583
  - St. Peters Church In file No. 1507
  - St. Stephen's Church In file No. 1507
  - Saint Tammany Farmer Page 407
  - Sait, Edward N. Pages 403a | 407a | 516d | 592 | 596 | 598 | 611 | 799
  - Salberg, Thoreald Page 545
  - Sandern, Julis L. Page 778
  - Sanford (Mr.), President of Warwick Historical Society Page 408
  - Sanford, F.V. Page 598
  - Saturday Evening Post Pages 821 | 839
  - Sauer, E.M. Pages 409 | 516d | 596 | 598 | 635 | 675
  - Saxe, John Godfrey Page 885
  - Saxe, Martin Pages 885 | 911
  - Saxton, William A. In file No. 1507
  - Schaffer, R.J. Page 600
  - Schallenberger, A.C. Pages 647-673
  - Scheier, John H. Pages 825 | 838
  - Schelley, Paul D. Page 675
  - Schiver, G.C. Page 674
  - Schlesinger, L. Pages 596 | 598
  - Schnieder, Miss Page 692
  - Schulte's Book Store Pages 596 | 598 | 600 | 620 | 674 | 675 | 704 | 720 | 756 | 759 | 778
  - Schulte, Theo Page 411
  - Schuylkill Fishing Co. Page 675
  - Schwartz, Louis Pages 825 | 838
  - Schwarz, Herbert T. Pages 589 | 598
  - Scientific American Page 739
  - Sciotto, Gazette Co. Page 658
  - Scope, Frank J. Pages 771 | 779 | 786
  - Scott & O'Shaughnessey Pages 623 | 707 | 756 | 763 | 806 | 810
  - Scribner's & Sons, Charles Pages 412 | 413 | 517 | 675 | 756 | 839 | 911
  - Seagle, Rev. Nathan A. In file No. 1507
  - Sealle, A.T. Page 606
  - Secretary of State of NY Page 641
  - Secretary of State, Washington, D.C. Page 690
  - Secretary of the Navy Page 839
  - Senior, Mary Page 675
  - Servoss, G.H. Page 516d
  - Settel, Arthur Pages 893 | 910
  - Shapiro, A. Page 852
  - Sharp, R.F. Page 825
  - Shaw, Albert Page 756
  - Shaw, Robert G. Page 825
  - Shenk, H.H. Pages 884 | 910
  - Sherrill, Miles B. Page 343
  - Sherwood Co. Pages 739 | 561 | 761
  - Sherwood, George H. Pages 317 | 598
  - Shields, C.V. Page 825
  - Shotwell, James T. Page 592
  - Siebold, Louis Pages 414 | 415
  - Sierich, H.W. Page 771
  - Simmons, Thomas W. Page 655
  - Simons, B.F. Pages 736 | 756
  - Sinnott, John F. Page 839
  - Skinner, Milton Page 416
  - Slattery, E.J. Pages 534 | 545 | 598
  - Smith, A. Grant Page 591
  - Smith, Chandler Page 874
  - Smith, Major Chandler In file No. 1507
  - Smith, Edward C. Page 910
  - Smith, Edward C. In file No. 1507
  - Smith, Edward H. Pages 771 | 778 | 779 | 789 | 799 | 825 | 839
  - Smith, Elizabeth Page 606
  - Smith, James W. Page 778
  - Smith, John Talbot Page 779
  - Smith, Lloyd W. Page 878
  - Smith, R.H. Page 598
  - Smith, Thomas F. Pages 426 | 428 | 473a | 539 | 594 | 596 | 598 | 655 | 675 | 694 | 778
  - Smith, T.R. Page 838
  - Smith, Walter M. Page 596
  - Smithsonian Institute Pages 560 | 646 | 647 | 727
  - Snevily, H.M. Page 694
  - Society of Tammany or Columbian Order in the City of New York Pages 653 | 820 | 821
  - Sonneck, O.G. Page 257
  - South Carolina State Library Page 417
  - Speck, F.H. Pages 418 | 419 | 600
  - Spice Mill Publishing Co. Pages 739 | 765
  - Spinney, William Pages 632 | 653 | 674 | 675
  - "Spirit of the Missions" Page 566
  - Spitzer, Eugene R. Pages 596 | 598 | 626
  - Spofford, E.P. Page 757
  - Spofford, Florence Pages 596 | 597 | 598 | 599 | 621 | 623 | 644 | 675 | 697g |701
  - Spofford, Hartwell Page 592
  - Stanley, Augustus O. Page 799
  - State Historical Society of Wisconson Page 852
  - State Tax Department Page 821
  - Steagill, Henry B. Page 799
  - Steagill, Henry B. In file No. 1217
  - Stebbins, N.L. Pages 568 | 600 | 674 | 675 | 704
  - Stechert, G.E. & Co. Page 674
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmar Pages 873 | 911
  - Steiger & Co. Page 606
  - Stein, Morton Pages 885 | 910
  - Steinberg, N. Page 911
  - Steiner, Bernard C. Pages 420 | 421
  - Steinert, Charles M. Pages 825 | 839
  - Stephens, Francis X. Pages 893 | 908 | 911
  - Stephens & Brown Page 592
  - Stevens, H.L. Page 674
  - Stevenson, Archibold S. Page 910
  - Stevenson, Burton Pages 600 | 675
  - Stoddard, Lathrop Pages 886 | 887 | 888 | 889 | 890 | 891 | 910 | 911
  - Stokes, I.N. Phelps Page 756
  - Story of Tammany Page 820
  - Sullivan, Daniel V. Pages 825 | 839
  - Sullivan, James Pages 756 | 769
  - Sulzer, William Page 606
  - Sun (NY) Page 606
  - Superintendent of Documents, Washington D.C. Pages 639 | 693 | 697e | 838 | 839
  - Superintendent of Printing (Washington, D.C.) Page 911
  - Supreme Court of the State of New York Page 825
  - Survey Associates, Inc. Pages 403a | 422 | 424
  - Swain, Arthur Page 523
  - Swarts, Louis E. Pages 787 | 799 | 872 | 892
  - Swarts, Louis E. In file No. 1155
  - Sweeney, Peter B. Page 425
  - Taft, William H. Page 676
  - Tagne, Peter F. Page 602
  - Tammany & Columbian Order Page 817
  - Tammany Hall Pages 426 | 428 | 813 | 815
  - Tammany, James Pages 429 | 431
  - Tammany, Joseph Page 432
  - Tammany Loan Receipt, 1812 Page 820
  - Tammany Society Pages 547 | 815
  - Tammany Society, Johnston, PA Page 433
  - Tammany Society, Lexington, KY Page 434
  - Tammany Society, Portland, OR Page 435
  - Tammany Times Pages 435a | 773
  - Tammany, Warren Page 436
  - Tanner, Frederick C. Page 602
  - Taylor, Robert C. Page 839
  - Terrill, Jane Page 876
  - Thail Music Corporation Page 846
  - Theatrical Hall of Fame Pages 818 | 819 | 820
  - Thistle Press Page 911
  - Thomas, Charles S. Pages 602 | 755
  - Thompson, Charles Willis Pages 892 | 911
  - Thompson, John A. Pages 826 | 839 | 894 | 911
  - Tiernam, Bernard J. Pages 789 | 799
  - Times (NY) Pages 473a | 606 | 614
  - Times Union (Albany) Page 602
  - Toepp, Lawrence A. Pages 826 | 839 | 852
  - Tolman, Frank L. Pages 331 | 333 | 580
  - Toronto Public Library Page 569
  - Tracy, Howard E. Pages 696 | 702 | 755 | 761
  - Trent, W.P. Page 98
  - Tribune (NY) Pages 557 | 606
  - Trinity Church In file No. 1507
  - Tumulty, Joseph P. Page 601
  - Tuttle Co. Pages 877 | 879 | 900 | 909
  - Tuttle, Julius H. Pages 233a | 436 | 601 | 644 | 697e | 701a
  - Tyree, J.O. Pages 646 | 696
  - Tyson, James A. Pages 892 | 911
  - Underhill, Frank Page 623
  - Underhill Studio Pages 707 | 763
  - Underwood, Oscar W. Page 584
  - Unger, Albert Blogg Pages 826 | 840
  - United Library Association Page 839
  - United States, Census Bureau Pages 437 | 449
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Indian Affairs Pages 451 | 453 | 455 | 456
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Indian Service (Indian Industrial School, Carlisle, PA) Page 450
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Indians (Five Civilized Nations) Pages 454 | 455
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Pension Bureau Pages 457 | 463
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Post Office Department Pages 464 | 465
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Secretary of State Page 467
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Superintendent of Documents Pages 421a | 469
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Superintendent of Printing Page 421a
  - United States, Commerice and Labor, Weather Bureau Page 421a
  - United States Naval Academy Page 821
  - U.S. Press and Publicity Bureau Page 769
  - University Book Store Page 840
  - University of the State of New York Pages 656 | 726
  - Valentine, George R. Page 516a
  - Valentine's Manual of Old New York Page 815
  - Van, Miss J. Ingram Page 665
  - Vanguard Press Pages 894 | 904 | 934
  - Veteran's Corps of Artillery In file No. 1507
  - Victory, William J. Page 826
  - Virginia, Secretary of State of Pages 654 | 691
  - Virginia State Library Pages 472 | 473
  - Vollmer, William A. Pages 473a | 571 | 608
  - Voorhis, John R. Pages 474 | 519 | 601 | 608 | 643 | 787 | 840
  - Wade, Edward T. Page 475
  - Wadlin, Horace O. Pages 608 | 643
  - Wagner, Robert F. Pages 895 | 912
  - Wainwright, Richard, Jr. Pages 826 | 840
  - Wakeman, A. Pages 553 | 604 | 627 | 633 | 758
  - Walcott, Charles D. Page 727
  - Wall, A.J. Pages 740 | 773 | 783 | 799 | 826 | 840 | 895 | 912
  - Wall, A.J. In file No. 1507
  - Wallace, Schyler Page 799
  - Wallstein, Leonard M. Page 608
  - Walpole Galleries Page 763
  - Walsh, David F. In file No. 1217
  - Walsh, David I. Page 799
  - Walsh, Thomas Page 775
  - Walthart, J.L. Pages 476 | 479
  - Wandler, Gertrude E. Page 702
  - War Department Page 603
  - War Department In file No. 1507
  - Warner, James Page 820
  - Warwick Historical Society Pages 408 | 598
  - Washburn, J. Thomas Page 773
  - Watkins, Ann Pages 896 | 911 | 912
  - Wayne Independent Page 905
  - Wayte, Raymond Page 840
  - Weglin, Oscar Pages 480 | 486a-b | 516e | 604 | 607 | 609 | 613 | 623 | 644 | 647 | 676 | 684 | 685 | 696 | 701 | 706 | 707 | 722 | 758 | 765 | 773 | 799 | 810
  - Weil, David L. Page 517
  - Weintraub, Paul Pages 775 | 785 | 799
  - Weise, Arthur J. Pages 487 | 492 | 646 | 696
  - Wendel, Louis Pages 826 | 840
  - Wendell, Everet Jansen Pages 493 | 495
  - Wenman, A.M. Page 568
  - Werner, Charles J. Pages 799 | 810
  - West, D.H. Pages 516e | 684
  - West Publishing Co. Pages 840 | 912 | 934
  - West Side Democratic Club Page 927
  - Westervelt, L. Page 676
  - Whalen, Grover A. Page 775
  - Wheeler, Jesse F. Pages 696 | 697f
  - "White" Page 608
  - White, Bouck Page 496
  - White, Charles T. Page 840
  - White, Hammel Page 643
  - Whiten, E. Stagg Pages 497 | 498 | 604 | 607 | 609 | 670
  - Whiten, Frederick Pages 498a | 609
  - Whitlock's Book Store Pages 896 | 912
  - Who's Who Publications, Inc. Page 846
  - Wilder's Old Curiosity Shop Pages 498a | 684
  - Wiley, G.M. Page 615
  - Wilk, Jacob In file No. 1155
  - Wilkins "Back Number" Pages 676 | 685 | 705 | 758 | 768
  - Willard, Elsia May Page 758
  - Williams, Daniel C. Page 696
  - Williams, John Sharp Pages 607 | 609
  - Williams, Samuel C. Page 644
  - Williams, Samuel W. Pages 677 | 678 | 679 | 680 | 681 | 682 | 683 | 727
  - Williams, Talcott Pages 604 | 607 | 609
  - Wilson, H.W. Co. Pages 607 | 609 | 623 | 630 | 635 | 607
  - Wilson, James C. Page 775
  - Wilson, T. Webber Page 799
  - Wilson, William B. Page 775
  - Wilson, Woodrow Pages 604 | 608
  - Wingo, Otis Page 799
  - Wingo, Otis In file No. 1217
  - Winship, John Carter Pages 194 | 501a-b | 603
  - Wisconsin, Department of State Page 654
  - Wisconsin University Pages 569 | 596
  - Witmark, M. & Sons Pages 605 | 676 | 685 | 813 | 840
  - Wobast, E.S. Pages 607 | 609
  - Wohl, Mr. Page 758
  - Wolhagen, A.J. Pages 604 | 607 | 608 | 609 | 635 | 676 | 740 | 758
  - Wood, William R. Page 840
  - Woodell, Mark Page 607
  - Woods, Cyrus E. Pages 654 | 696
  - Woodward Page 799
  - "World" Pages 606 | 607
  - World's Work Pages 499 | 500
  - Wormser, Richard S. Pages 897 | 912
  - Wyer, J.T., Jr. Pages 334 | 607
  - Wyman, M.C. Page 826
  - Wyoming Historical & Geological Society Pages 501 | 513 | 676 | 685
  - Wyrell, Manton Page 609
  - Ye Olde Bronx Booke Shoppe Page 548
  - Young, Horace G. Page 912
  - Zieback, Zula Page 740